

Surrey, UK 07935408399

zoepointon123@gmail.com

zoeellenpointon.com



Python

D3

Microsoft Excel

UX SKILLS

User Journeys Prototyping User Testing Focus Groups

DEV SKILLS

HTML CSS

DESIGN SOFTWARE

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign After Effects

XD

Sketch Invision

Zeplin

Balsamic

REFERENCES

BETTINA NISSEN

University of Edinburgh bettina.nissen@ed.co.uk

ALLAN CRABTREE

TruDigital

allan@allancrabtree.co.uk

SALLY HANSON

CDG

sally@shml.co.uk



PERSONAL STATEMENT

Currently studying a masters in Design Informatics, at the University of Edinburgh. Two years experience working within the Tech Industry. Graduated from the University of Winchester with a first class honours in Digital Media Design.

Looking for a new challenge in user experience or analytics, working with data, starting September 2019.

EXPERIENCE

TruDigital, Portsmouth - UX/UI Designer APR 2018 - JUL 2018

Formerly part of CDG. My role in the company was to design and build websites for our SME clients. Working in a start-up setting allowed me to take greater ownership of client projects. I also took a lead role in streamlining the design/development process for the 'affordable' website offering.

CDG, Sunningdale - Graduate Designer MAY 2017 - APR 2018

After graduating I joined CDG as a graduate designer. My role expanded to running client meetings, preparing and conducting focus groups and user testing. As well as working on client projects, I also got the opportunity to work within product teams, creating and refining digital products using agile.

CDG, Sunningdale - Digital Design Intern MAY 2016 - APR 2017

During my last year at university I got the opportunity to work alongside my study. It allowed me to develop my design and problem solving skills and gain new experience creating design mock-ups and prototypes for clients.

EDUCATION

SEP 2018 - AUG 2019

University of Edinburgh - MA Design Informatics

Predicted Grade: Merit

SEP 2014 - MAY 2017

University of Winchester - BA Digital Media Design

Grade: First